Devdeepsinh Ashoksinh Jadeja

♥ Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India ■ devdeepjadeja2001@gmail.com 🔲 9512373391 🛅 in/devdeepsinh-jadeja-0591

jadejadevdeepsinha591.github.io/Portfolio-Devdeepsinh-Jadeja/

SUMMARY

A Self-motivated IT developer with 3+ years of professional experience in software analysis, design, and development using Microsoft ASP.NET Domain. Capable of developing both client and server portions of large & small-scale applications. significantly expediting project timelines while maintaining rigorous quality standards. Giving my best to Organizations with 100% effort.

EXPERIENCE

Junior Software Engineer

Qeleo Technolabs

January 2022 - Present, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- Developed custom applications using the .NET framework for increased functionality and enhanced the user experience within the organization.
- Contributed to the development of scalable and maintainable .NET applications using:- C# & ASP.NET Core/MVC, JavaScript/jQuery, Ajax, CSS/Bootstrap and SQL Server, Web API/REST.
- · Collaborated with cross-functional teams to develop, end user-friendly interfaces that facilitated seamless navigation for end-users.
- · Increased system stability through rigorous debugging and troubleshooting of complex issues within the .NET framework.
- Developed reusable code libraries/components that expedited development time for future projects by providing ready-to-use resources.
- Conducted thorough testing to identify bugs and ensure optimal functionality before deploying web applications into production environments.
- · Contributed to innovative solutions with thoughtful problem-solving techniques & completed products within the project deadline.
- Utilized modern front-end frameworks such as React or Angular to create modular, scalable UI components

Web Developer Intern

InfoLabz IT Services Pvt. Ltd

May 2021 - July 2021, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- Wrote custom HTML and JavaScript for existing websites.
- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5, and CSS3.
- Developed interactive prototypes using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery for client presentations and feedback sessions.
- Studied user requirements to gain a strong understanding of project initiatives and deadlines.
- Followed best practices for software development and web security. Implemented responsive design techniques to adapt web applications for multiple devices, enhancing user experience and achieving a 15% increase in mobile user engagement over a 3-month period.

PROJECT

Portfolio Website

jadejadevdeepsinha591.github.io/Portfolio-Devdeepsinh-Jadeja/ • May 2021 - July 2021

- Features:- It's a Personal Portfolio website with all the required information.
- GitHub:- https://github.com/JadejaDevdeepsinhA591/Portfolio-Devdeepsinh-Jadeja
- Category:- Personal
- Engineered a dynamic portfolio website utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript/jQuery, Ajax, and MySQL that showcased professional achievements and skills, with integrated APIs to enhance visitor interaction and data retrieval efficiency.

Education Resources Management System

eduresource.ml/ • January 2021 - March 2021

- **Features:** The product enables direct resource sharing between both end users and organizations with their own dashboard support, & it ensures the supply of all educational resources on a timely, cost-free, and commission-free basis without third-party involvement.
- GitHub:- https://github.com/Devdeepsinh0591/Education-Resource-Sharing-System
- Category:- Personal
- Engineered a comprehensive Education Resources Management System using the .NET framework, facilitating seamless resource sharing with integrated APIs and reusable plugins, enhancing accessibility for educational organizations.

Covid Cases Tracker

GIT Institute ORG Project • August 2020 - October 2020

- GitHub:- https://github.com/Devdeepsinh0591/Covid-cases-tracker
- **Features:** Engineered an automated Covid Cases Tracker web app utilizing React that delivered real-time state-wise Covid statistics in India, resulting in a 40% increase in user engagement and enhancing public information access through intuitive data visualization.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Engineering

Gujarat Technological University • Gandhinagar, Gujarat, India • 2022 • CGPA:- 8.06

Graduation with Distinction

High School

Minor in Mathematics • Gujarat Higher Secondary Education Board • Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India • 2018

Mathematics

CERTIFICATIONS

Web Application Development

Coursera • 2021

Data Structures & Algorithms (Fundamentals)

Coursera • 2021

• Certified to maintain applications using Data Structures & Algorithms & their future use-cases to improve our application more reliable.

SKILLS

Software: Asp .NET, .NET Core, MVC, Webforms, LINQ, Ado .NET, WPF/WCF, SignalR Ajax, Entity Framework, Microservices, Web API, REST/SOAP.

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, C#, Java(basics).

Database:- SQL Server/MySQL. **SQL:-** T-SQL, SSRS/SSMS

Version Control: Visual Studio, Git, GitHub.

Other:- Team Collaboration, Interpersonal Communication.